setgame.com 2019-08-28

# Privacy Policy | America's Favorite Card Games®

Your privacy is important to us. At Set Enterprises, Inc., we value your privacy and have made it our policy to provide a secure online environment and to provide online content that requires minimal collection of information from our visitors. We have adopted an Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") that guides how we collect, store and use information you provide us online.

**Submission of any form on our site constitutes acceptance of the  [Mollom privacy policy](https://www.mollom.com/web-service-privacy-policy)** **.**

**Children**  
We take seriously our responsibility to our many young consumers. Our website has been designed to be accessible, safe for kids of all ages, and to adhere to all applicable laws and regulations. Children under the age of 13 and their parents should review the section of this policy called "Note to Parents About Children's Privacy" which discusses the special steps we take for young children who visit our site.

**What type of information does Set Enterprises, Inc. collect?**  
Set Enterprises, Inc. does not require you to share personal information to enjoy our website. That means you can visit our website without any need to register with us. However, registration is required to participate in contests on our website.

The information we gather falls into two categories: (1) personal information you voluntarily supply when you order, enter the daily puzzle contest, or provide your e-mail address and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our site.

_Personally Identifiable Information (PII)_  
Anyone can view our website, but a free registration process is required to enter our daily puzzle contest. You must be at least 18 years old to enter our daily puzzle contest.  If you wish to enter our daily puzzle contest you must register by supplying an e-mail address, creating a username and password and providing us with your name and address. 

To enable the purchase of items from our online store, we collect billing and credit card information, including your name, address, telephone number, and credit card number. You must be at least 18 years old to purchase items from our online store. This information will only be shared with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase transaction. Examples of this include processing credit card payments.

_Aggregate Information Collected Through Technology_  
A "cookie" is a small file that we save on your computer's hard drive that contains non-personal information. Set Enterprises, Inc. uses cookies to store login information to allow easier and faster access for returning users.

**Google Analytics Privacy Notice**  
Our website uses Google Analytics to collect information about the use of our website. Google Analytics collects information from users such as age, gender, interests, demographics, how often they visit our website, what pages they visit, and what other websites they have used before coming to our website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to analyze traffic, remarket our products and services to users, improve our marketing, advertising, and to improve our website. We have enabled Google Analytics features such as Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our website, not your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected using Google Analytics with PII. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google also uses specific identifiers to help collect information about the use of our website. For more information on how Google collects and processes your data, visit <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>

You can prevent Google Analytics from using your information by opting out at this link: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

**Who is collecting the information?**  
Set Enterprises, Inc. collects the personal information you share on our website. We will use the information you submit to send you advertising or promotional materials, including information about new products, contests, features and enhancements, special offers and other events of interest. We also use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies so we can improve the products and services we provide.

**With whom does Set Enterprises, Inc. share my personal information?**  
Set Enterprises, Inc. will only share your personally identifiable information with entities that use it solely to provide support for the internal operations of the Set Enterprises, Inc. website (i.e., email services, credit card processing or technical support). These entities will not use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose, and have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, including but not limited to disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability.

Set Enterprises, Inc. does not sell, rent or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information collected from our website to third parties other than stated above. However, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, Set Enterprises, Inc.'s customer information may be transferred to Set Enterprises, Inc.'s successor or assign, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

**Our commitment to data security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Review, update and removal of personal information**  
If you have registered with our site, you may at any time review, update and/or delete the contact information we have for you in our database. This can be accomplished by editing your user profile from our website.

**Changes to this policy**  
This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If we make a significant or material changes in the way we use your personal information, the change will be posted on this page thirty (30) days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via e-mail.

**NOTE TO PARENTS ABOUT CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**  
Set Enterprises, Inc. has made every effort to ensure that both adults and children can use and enjoy our website. We do not collect personal information from children under the age of 13. We encourage you to discuss this privacy statement with your children.

**Collection and use of children's personal information**  
Only those 18 and older are allowed to register for the daily puzzle contest or create an account to purchase items from our online store.
